tradereader.com 2019-06-01

# Live Tender, Tender, Tender Bids, Municipal Corporation Tender, Fresh Tenders, Tenders Online

**TradeReader.com** and its PROMOTORS **Anmol Infra Soft Inc** is committed to protecting your privacy and security.

**Use of Personal & Business Information** We may require your personal information from time to time in order for us to provide you with our services such as Tender Alerts on Email, Tender Via Web Search, Trial services, Business listing services, Business promotion services like advertising, newsletters etc.

**TradeReader.com's** primary goal in collecting personal or public information is to provide the user with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalization services, interactive communications and many other types of services. Business information may be used to display the user's business listing or product offerings across our network to fetch maximum business opportunities for the user. 

In order to provide such services, Tradereader.com may display advertisements based upon the site usage statistics and visitor trends. **TradeReader.com** uses user's personal & business information to serve targeted advertisements through its website, newsletters and customized mailers. In addition to it, once the user's personal and business information is displayed on our network, the user may start receiving business enquiries from various buyers and sellers that might or might not be of their interest. WE do not exercise any control over its users for sending business enquiries to the listed members.

In order to deliver such services, we will have to process and store your personal information and may need to transfer it to the relevant partner(s), affiliates of **TradeReader.com** for processing domestic as well as overseas. By submitting your personal information, you consent to such processing and transfer in connection with such orders, offers or services and for any other purposes. We will never willfully disclose personal information about you to any third party other than to process an order or unless we are under a legal obligation to do so. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that **TradeReader.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Monitoring, Logs & Cookies** We at **TradeReader.com** use IP address cookies etc. to analyze trends, administer the site, track site use, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

If you have any comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or want copy of information we hold about you, feel free to contact us.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically.
